http://www.canadasoccer.com/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using this website. This policy explains the type of
personal information we collect from you, how it is used, and the steps
we take to ensure your personal information is handled appropriately.
Please also take time to read this site’s Terms of Services.
For purposes of this Privacy Policy, Canada Soccer refers to the Canadian Soccer Association.
Canada
Soccer members are independent associations and are responsible for
adopting their own privacy policies. Canada Soccer online store is
managed and operated by NAME and is responsible for adopting its own
privacy policy.
Canada Soccer reserves the right to change this
Privacy Policy at any time by posting the revised Privacy Policy on
canadasoccer.com.
What is personal information?
Personal
Information is information that refers to an individual specifically and
is recorded in any form. Personal information includes such things as
age, income, birth date, medical records, credit records.
Collection of personal information
Canada
Soccer does not automatically collect personal information such as your
name, address, telephone number or email address when you visit this
site. Such information will be collected by Canada Soccer if you provide
it to us in order to:
participate in forums or discussionsreceive our newsletterenter a contest or promotionrequest information from us.
We do not require that any personal information be provided in order to view our website.
Canada Soccer collects only the personal information required to provide products and services to you.
If
the personal information we require is collected for a reason other
than to provide products and services, your consent will be requested at
or before the time the information is collected. Examples of reasons we
collect personal information include:
to respond to your inquiries and send you requested informationto provide products and services you requestto allow you to participate in contests and promotionsto protect against fraud and errorto recommend products and services that Canada Soccer believes will be of interest to youto comply with legal and government regulations.
Retention of personal information
Canada
Soccer does not sell or rent personal information to any organization
or person for any reason. We do not share your personal information
without your consent with any third party organizations except to offer
you products or services we believe will be of interest to you.
Canada
Soccer retains your personal information only as long as it is required
for our business relationship or as required by federal or provincial
laws.
You can change your consent preferences at any time or
request access to the personal information we have on record in order to
review and amend the information by contacting media@canadasoccer.com.
Cookies
Like
many organizations, Canada Soccer uses cookie technology on our site. A
“cookie” is a unique identifier collected by the site to verify a
returning visitor’s identity, or to understand how visitors navigate the
site. The use of cookies is standard on the Internet and many major
websites use them (You can visit the Network Advertising Initiative if
you want to find out more information about this practice). Most web
browsers automatically accept cookies. You can usually change your
browser to prevent or notify you whenever you are sent a cookie. This
gives you the chance to decide whether or not to accept the cookie.
A
cookie does not tell us who you are, your email address, or any other
personal information. We use the information it provides to help us
improve the site and our service, and to provide our visitors with a
better website visit. We do not share information obtained through
cookies with any third parties.
We have no control over the
content of third party websites that individuals may access through
hyperlinks at our website. We encourage everyone to read the privacy
policy of every website they visit.
Even without accepting a
cookie you can still access most of the features on the site. There may,
however, be limitations on your use of some site functions.
Links to other websites
This
site may contain links to websites of third parties. Canada Soccer is
not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such
websites.
By using canadasoccer.com, you are consenting to the information collection and use described in this policy.
Contact
If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact our media@canadasoccer.com.
Guidelines for the Return to Soccer
Canada Soccer outlines return to soccer guidelines. The return to soccer guidelines provide member organizations with a five-step process, including a checklist of weighted questions known as the Return to Soccer Assessment Tool.
SEE GUIDELINES
Articles You May Also Like
AWARDS AND RECOGNITION
AWARDS AND RECOGNITION
Christine Sinclair’s record-breaking goal named Canada Soccer Moment of the Year
December 10, 2020
WOMEN'S NATIONAL TEAM
WOMEN'S NATIONAL TEAM
Canadians start 2020-21 UEFA Women’s Champions League season
December 09, 2020
AWARDS AND RECOGNITION
AWARDS AND RECOGNITION
Alphonso Davies co-winner for Lou Marsh Trophy as the best in Canada
We use cookies to ensure the best experience on our website. By continuing, you agree to the terms set out in our privacy policy.Ok
